velumani.com 2015-03-16

# Privacy Policy | Dr. A Velumani's Personal Website - A Creator and Founder of Thyrocare

* * *

For all the users accessing www.velumani.com website, we are committed to protecting your privacy. This privacy policy enlists all the details which will be collected on accessing and browsing the site along with the way in which the information will be collected, stored and shared. By accessing the website, you agree and consent to the collection, storage and sharing of your personally identifiable information as described in this policy.  
In case you disagree with the terms and clauses in this policy, do not access the website (www.velumani.com). The terms of the privacy policy mentioned are applicable to the said website only.

1\. The clauses of the policy may be changed from time to time and we reserve the rights to incorporate changes and modifications in the existing policy. It is the user responsibility to access and read the privacy policy each time the website is accessed, to ensure familiarity with current version.

2\. When you visit and browse the site, no personally identifiable information would be collected. However, we will still be receiving and storing some non-personal information. You will be allowed to post your comments in the site under tabs dedicated for the same. During such postings, you will be prompted to share your email address. Such content posted by the user will be open and available for other users who access the tab. The content posted by you, may be re-posted by other users, and even on account of the comment being deleted by you, copy will be retained in the cache memory.

3\. You may also be required to share your email address in order to receive communications from us. All the email communications from our side will have a link for unsubscribing which you may click to opt out of our future emails. These email communications from us may be pertaining to promotions, offers, services or response to your inquiries submitted. Even when you opt out of email communications from us, all of your personally identifiable information will be stored by us and will be used to resolve disputes and in issues pertaining to security and law enforcements as and when required. All such information collected may be retained for an indefinite period of time by us and may be disposed off any time without prior notice.

4\. Users can also provide their feedback, comments, opinions and questions in the “contact us” link in the website. While submitting the form, you will be required to provide your name and email address. With such submissions you consent to us storing your personally identifiable information voluntarily.

5\. Some automatically collected non-identifiable information each time you visit and browse the website include the IP address, your domain name, the date and time of access, your internet host, your operating system information and the pages visited. Such information is used for identifying and for trouble shooting purposes pertaining to the server in our end.

6\. The site may use third party cookie to record information about the users activities in the site and also to “remember” the user when they return to the site. These cookies are stored as small files in the users computer for record keeping, while some like session ID cookies are temporary and expire on terminating the browsing. Personally identifiable information cannot be collected via this cookie tracking technology unless previously shared information has been tied to the cookie. The collated cookie data may be shared with third parties. We are not responsible and do not control the information collected and used by such third parties.

7\. In order to protect privacy of the users accessing and browsing the said website, we assure that none of the personally identifiable and non-identifiable information collected will be shared with any third party for marketing purposes. However, we may share your information with our affiliated partners and service providers, the use of which is subject to the privacy policy agreement with them.

8\. All the information of the user recorded and shared on the website is saved securely in our server and is not accessible to the general public. Such information is available to be viewed only by a limited number of authorized staff and other agents, but not without a confidentiality agreement with the said party.

9\. All the contents posted in the site are intended to be accessed and browsed by adults/near adults. For users who are not adults, accessing the website without an adult supervision is prohibited. Any information posted by such minors if collected unknowingly in our website, will be immediately deleted from our server.

10\. In case of further queries regarding our privacy policy clauses, feel free to contact us by clicking on the Contact link in the footer section of our website.
